wildblue.com 2004-12-05

# WildBlue Communications - Privacy Policy

As of November 15, 2003, WildBlue updated its Privacy Policy to give you a better understanding of our Privacy Policy and Practice. If you have any questions, please contact WildBlue directly. 

Introduction    
We at WildBlue and our affiliated companies ("WildBlue") are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. 

WildBlue has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. 

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit WildBlue's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. 

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the Web, we may transfer that Information within WildBlue or to WildBlue's third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.   
  Top of Page

* * *

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies   
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site. 

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.   
  Top of Page

* * *

Third Party Services   
Third parties provide certain services available on WildBlue.com on WildBlue's behalf. WildBlue may provide information, including Personal Information, that WildBlue collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which WildBlue maintains its Web site and mailing lists. WildBlue will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on WildBlue's behalf.   
  Top of Page

* * *

Your Consent   
By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to WildBlue's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where WildBlue collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.   
  Top of Page

November 15, 2003
